Guide to the Science Fiction and Comic Fanzine Collection, 1952-2005 SC.1980.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Science Fiction Fanzines, 1966-1982; II.
  - SOG: Son of Grafan, 1974; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Published in St. Louis, MO. Affiliated with Grafan.
  - Son of Glop, 1972; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Published in Grove City, PA and edited by Jeff Schalles.
  - Space and Time, 1972; 2 issues (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Published in Kew Gardens, NY and edited by Gordon and Rebecca Linzer.
  - The Spanish Imposition, 1976; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Published in Miffletown, NY and edited by Dave Romm and Andrew Porter.
  - Spanish Inquisition, 1975; 7 issues (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Jerry Kaufman and Suzanne Tompkins.
  - Speculation, 1971-1973; 5 issues (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Published in Birmingham, UK and edited by Peter R. Weston.
  - Speculative Poetry Review, 1977; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Published in Nantucket, MA and edited by Robert Frazier.
  - Speculative Science Fiction Newsletter, 1980; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Published in Redfield, SD and edited by Kathleen Taylor.
  - Squa Tront, 1968-1974; 4 issues (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Published in Wichita, KS and edited by Jerry Weist and John Benson.
  - Star Line, 1978-1979; 15 issues (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Published in Leucadia, CA and edited by Suzette Haden Elgin for the Science Fiction Poetry Association.
  - Star Trek Giant Poster Book, 1976-1977; 10 issues (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Ron Barlow.
  - Starburger, 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 29)
    Published in Grahamsville, NY and edited by Elena Pirov. A collection of fanzines by different authors.
  - Starburst Magazine, 1978-1979; 5 issues (Box 10, Folder 30)
    Published in London, UK and edited by Dez Skinn.
  - Starstone, 1978; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Published in Berkeley, CA and edited by Marion Zimmer Bradley and Walter Breen for the Friends of Darkover.
  - Starstream, 1976; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Edited by Roger Elwood.
  - Stems, 1977; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Published in Santa Monica, CA and edited by Alan Benson Williams.
  - Sthondat, 1979; 2 issues (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Published in Westlake Village, CA and edited by Eddie Anderson.
  - Street Life, 1975; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 35)
    Published in High Holborn, London, UK and edited by Billy Walker.
  - Styx, 1973; 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 36)
    Published in Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada and edited by Joseph Krolik.
  - Syntax, 1 issue (Box 10, Folder 37)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Christopher McQuire and Dan Recchia.
  - Syzgy, 1968; 2 issues (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Published in Bridgeville, PA and edited by Peter Hays and Art Vaughan for the Western Pennsylvania Science Fiction Association.
  - TA of SP: The Anthology of Speculative Poetry, 1978; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Edited by Robert Frazier.
  - Tanjent, 1978; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Published in Wanganui, New Zealand and edited by Greg Hills.
  - Tesseract, 1977; 2 issues (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Published in Chicago, IL and edited by K.W. MacAnn, Robert Garcia, Cory Glaberson and Nancy K-Zinserling.
  - Tetragrammatron Fragments, 1979; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Published in New York, NY and edited by Jay Zilber.
  - This Is Legend, 1971; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Published in Champaign, IL and edited by Richard L. Jennings.
  - Tholian Web, 1971-1973; 4 issues (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Published in Erie, PA and edited by Jo-Anne Bonesteel and Sylvia Stanczyk.
  - Thunderbolt, 1976; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and New York, NY and edited by Ben Ruiz and Tom Tuttle.
  - Tightbeam, 1977-1981; 12 issues (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Published in Pompton Lakes, NJ and edited by Lynne Holdom. Joint issue with TNFF housed with TNFF issues.
  - TNFF: The National Fantasy Fan, 1977-1981; 12 issues (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
    Published in Lake Jackson, TX and edited by Joanne Burger, Donald Franson, Owen K. Laurion and Nick Grassel. Includes joint issue with TIghtbeam.
  - Tolkien Journal, 1966-1967; 5 issues (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY by the Tolkien Society of America and edited by Richard Plotz and Richard C. West. Also called the Orcist. Includes a subzine called Green Dragon.
  - Tribes, 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Dale and Dennis DiNucci.
  - True Facts, 1979; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Published in Madison, WI and edited by Diane Martin.
  - True Fan Adventure Theater, 1973; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Published in Brooklyn, NY and edited by Tony Isabella.
  - Tuesdaily, 1973; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - T.V. Sci-Fi Monthly, 1976; 6 issues (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Published in London, UK and edited by Don Atyeo and Mick Faran.
  - Universe, 1973-1974; 2 issues (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Edited by Joel Fischer.
  - Unmutual, 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Published in Jackson, MI and edited by Wally Stoelting.
  - Venture, 1975; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Published in San Jose, CA and edited by Frank Cirocro and Gary Winnick.
  - Vertex, 1973-1975; 4 issues (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Published in Los Angeles, CA and edited by Donald J. Pfeil.
  - Voice of the Lobster, 1978-1980; 5 issues (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Published in Cambridge, MA and edited by George Flynn.
  - VOR-ZAP, 3 issues (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Published in Lafayette, IN and edited by Walter Daniels.
  - Vorpal Sword, 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Published in Arlington, Va and edited by Jack Howard Lechner.
  - Weirdbook, 1971; 2 issues (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Published in Chambersburg, MD and edited by W. Paul Ganley.
  - WHA, 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Whizzard, 1977; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Published in St. Louis, MO and edited by Marty Klug.
  - Wife Styles and Life Styles, 1974; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 27)
    Published in Trona, CA. Written by Frank M. Darrow.
  - Windhaven, 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Published in Seattle, WA.
  - Witchcraft and Sorcery, 1971-1974; 6 issues (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Published in Alhambra, CA and edited by Gerald W. Page. Formerly Coven 13.
  - WOOPS, 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 30)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Linda E. Bushyager.
  - WPSFA Science Monitor, 1974; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 31)
    Published in Pittsburgh, PA and edited by Bob Ruben and Henry Roll.
  - Zelot, 1980; 1 issue (Box 11, Folder 32)
    Published by Bactrians Enterprises in Norway and edited by Ragnar Fyri AKA Supwith. Includes a subzine called Zelook.
- Related Materials, III.
  This series inlcludes materials related to conventions, fanclub newsletters, and advertising materials for science fiction movies and books.
  - Advertisements (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Conventions (Box 11, Folder 34-38)
  - Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Fan Associations and Club News (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Star Trek Poster (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Sci-Fi Book Catalogs (Box 11, Folder 42-43)